THE RESISTANCE FIGHTING AGAINST THE
FIRST ORDER USED DISTINCTIVE RANK
BADGES
THESE GRAY RECTANGLES SPORTED RED
MARKINGS FOR ARMY OFFICERS AND
BLUE FOR NAVY
GENERAL LEIA ORGANA HOWEVER NOTABLY
WORE A RANKFREE VEST
RESISTANCE COMMAND OFFICERS DONNED BROWN
UNIFORMS FEATURING REPURPOSED REBEL STARBIRDS
WHILE MEDICAL PERSONNEL WORE DARKER
UNIFORMS WITH ARMBANDS
GROUND LOGISTICS STAFF SPORTED FADEDYELLOW
JACKETS WITH JUNIOR AND LEAD
DISPATCHERS IN MODIFIED OFFICER UNIFORMS
THESE BADGES AND UNIFORMS APPEARED
THROUGHOUT THE RESISTANCES STRUGGLE AS
SEEN IN VARIOUS FILMS COMICS
AND NOVELS