DEEP WITHIN WILD SPACE LIES
MULITA
A FORESTED PLANET TEEMING WITH
THE DRENGIR SENTIENT CARNIVOROUS PLANTS
THIS IS THEIR HOMEWORLD RULED
BY THE GREAT PROGENITOR THE
FIRST DRENGIR
AN ANCIENT AMAXINE TRANSPORT POD
SYSTEM INTENDED TO COMBAT THE
DRENGIR
BACKFIRED
INADVERTENTLY ALLOWING THE CREATURES TO
INFILTRATE AN AMAXINE SPACE STATION
LATER DURING THE HIGH REPUBLIC
ERA
JEDI KNIGHTS DEZ RYDAN AND
REATH SILAS DISCOVERED MULITA WHILE
INVESTIGATING THIS STATION
NARROWLY ESCAPING WITH THEIR LIVES
AFTER ENCOUNTERING THE DRENGIR
THE PLANETS CONNECTION TO A
SPREADING DRENGIR INFESTATION ACROSS THE
GALAXY LED JEDI MASTER AVAR
KRISS TO LAUNCH A MAJOR
ASSAULT ON MULITA
A STRATEGIC MOVE KNOWN TO
THE NIHIL WHO EXPLOITED THE
JEDIS ABSENCE TO ATTACK ELSEWHERE
MULITAS STORY FIRST HINTED AT
IN INTO THE DARK
WAS LATER FULLY REVEALED IN
VARIOUS HIGH REPUBLIC BOOKS AND
COMICS
SOLIDIFYING ITS PLACE AS A
PIVOTAL LOCATION IN THE CONFLICT