IN THE YEAR
ABY THE IMPERIALALIGNED WORLDS GATHERED
FOR A CRUCIAL DIPLOMATIC CONCLAVE
ON PHELARION HOSTED BY THE
FORMIDABLE THALASSA TARKIN
AMONG THE ATTENDEES SECRETLY DISGUISED
AS LERNA WAS PRINCESS LEIA
ORGANA HERSELF
THE LAVISH BANQUET WAS DRAMATICALLY
DISRUPTED BY AN EXPLODING PATCH
OF MEGONITE MOSS
CASTING A SHADOW OVER THIS
ALREADY TENSE MEETING AMIDST THE
GALACTIC CIVIL WAR
KEY FIGURES INCLUDED DARTH VADER
AND OTHER POWERFUL LEADERS LIKE
SHEA HUBLIN AND QUA MZERC
THIS EVENT SANDWICHED BETWEEN MISSIONS
TO TATOOINE AND THE SUBSEQUENT
DEVASTATION OF RION PROVED A
PIVOTAL MOMENT IN THE ONGOING
CONFLICT