TONGOR A DARKSKINNED HUMAN MALE
BOUNTY HUNTER AND TWIN BROTHER
OF TONGA FOUND HIMSELF CAUGHT
IN A DEADLY WEB OF
BETRAYAL
WORKING ALONGSIDE NAKANO LASH AND
OTHER NOTORIOUS HUNTERS LIKE BOBA
FETT AND BOSSK
HE PARTICIPATED IN A MISSION
TO ATTACK AN UNBROKEN CLAN
SANCTUARY ON CORELLIA
A JOB ORCHESTRATED BY THE
MOURNERS WAIL SYNDICATE HEIR KHAMUS
HOWEVER
LASHS TRUE MOTIVES WERE REVENGE
AND SHE KILLED KHAMUS
TONGOR REALIZING THE MISSIONS FAILURE
AND LASHS TREACHERY ALERTED THE
OTHER BOUNTY HUNTERS
INITIATING A CHAOTIC ESCAPE
DURING THE GETAWAY
BOBA FETT ATTEMPTED TO ELIMINATE
LASH
BUT A SHOT INTENDED FOR
THE NAUTOLAN INSTEAD FATALLY STRUCK
TONGOR
YEARS LATER HIS SISTER TONGA
UNAWARE OF THE TRUE CIRCUMSTANCES
SOUGHT REVENGE AGAINST LASH FOR
HIS DEATH
EVENTUALLY LEARNING THE TRUTH AND
FORGING A NEW PATH
TONGOR KNOWN FOR HIS RED
CLOTHING WHITE GAUNTLETS WITH ADVANCED
COMMS JAMMING TECHNOLOGY AND CLOSE
BOND WITH HIS TWIN
LEFT A LASTING IMPACT ON
THE GALAXYS CRIMINAL UNDERWORLD
ULTIMATELY SHAPING HIS SISTERS DESTINY